traderjoes.com 2015-12-07

# Privacy Policy | Trader Joe's

### Trader Joe’s Privacy Practices & Commitments

**10/06/14**

At Trader Joe’s, we understand that you care how information about you is used and shared. We care, too. As such, we make sure we safeguard your personally identifiable information and honor your requests for privacy. The following note outlines our privacy practices and commitments:

**Contact Information for The Fearless Flyer, e-newsletter Communications, and the TJ’s App** When you sign up to receive the Trader Joe’s Fearless Flyer and/or our e-newsletter or the TJ’s App, we store your personally identifiable information (such as name, mailing address and/or email) in an electronic database, which is for **Trader Joe’s use only (we’ll describe what we do with this information in a minute).** If at any time you do not want to receive our Fearless Flyer or E-newsletter, please update your preferences here.

**Site Navigation**  
Trader Joe’s may collect, store and accumulate certain information concerning your use of our websites and/or our app. This would include information regarding which of our pages, contests or promotions you access the most often and are most popular among our users. The one and only reason that we collect this information is to learn how we can better enhance our offerings to and communications with you. That’s it.

**Cookies (not the edible kind)**  
Whenever you interact on our site, we receive and store certain information in the form of Internet “cookies.” You can’t eat them and neither can we. Cookies are stored on your hard drive—not on our site—in the form of a text file (they are not harmful, nor tasty). They can help us understand your browsing patterns, which allows us to provide targeted information about products and pricing. Most cookies are “session cookies,” meaning that they are automatically deleted at the end of a session when you close your browser. Some cookies are called “persistent” cookies because they do not expire when you close your browser. Don’t worry, though—you can remove them by following directions provided in your Internet browser’s “help” file.  
We do NOT use cookies to examine your surfing behavior before or after leaving the Trader Joe’s website. We have better things to do.

Trader Joe’s uses the information it receives to better serve you and other customers.

**With Trader Joe’s Employees**  
Access to customer information is limited to employees who need it for a business purpose, such as to serve customers or maintain our information systems. All employees are committed to following our Privacy Practices. That means employees will only use customer information to better serve you.

**With Trader Joe’s Partners**  
We may also provide a list of names and addresses to a mail house so that they can send our newsletter from us to you. We may also share information with companies we have contracted with to provide technology services. Any partner that we work with would be required to sign a nondisclosure agreement that would prohibit them from disclosing the information we provide them to anyone else.

**With Other Parties**  
Other than in the above situations, we may release your information ONLY if you request or authorize us to do so. We may also release customer information when we believe it is necessary to comply with the law, enforce our legal rights; or to protect our customers or us. **We will NEVER sell your personal information to anyone, for any reason, at any time. Never.**

**What About Links to Third-Party Websites?**  
Our site sometimes provides links to websites that are operated solely by third parties that are not under our control. These Privacy Practices apply to our site only, and is not intended to describe the privacy policies of any third party sites.

**We Are Serious About The Security of Your Information:**  
We make reasonable efforts to ensure that your personal information is protected while you are on our site. We have security procedures in the storage and disclosure of personal information, which are designed to prevent unauthorized access. **It’s exactly the kind of protection that what we would want, if we were surfing the web on another site.** It’s really that simple.

**Changes in Our Privacy Practices and Commitments**  
We are always improving and updating our website to further enhance your experience. As a result, our policies will continue to evolve. As we implement new technology and provide new services, we will update our Privacy Practices & Commitments accordingly. Any changes to our Privacy Practices & Commitments will take effect upon posting. We encourage you to refer to this page on an ongoing basis for our most current policy and practices.

**Your Part**  
By using our website, you are consenting to the collection, use and sharing of the information described in this statement of Privacy Practices & Commitments. We appreciate your trust in us and we promise to protect it fervently.
